# TRAPTI RAHANDGALE

## **SKILLS**

Frontend Engineer with over 2.5 + years of experience with broad skill set in UI and Interactive Development.

Worked with SAAS apps and consumer facing web application interfaces.

Working closely with designers, developers and managers to create variety of web based projects.

Have experience working on a variety of web based responsive apps using technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript, jQuery, React. With focus on Accessibility, Usability, Cross Browser Compatibility, Responsive Web, Twitter Bootstrap, Mobile first approach, Test coverage, Performance and SEO.

Enforcing practices/patterns & coding standards in the products.

Becoming better at frontend performance, writing frontend tests, going deeper with react redux patterns, Accessibility.

Good at learning new technologies, implementing the same and writing on <a href="Medium">Medium</a> about it.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Quintype Technologies, Bengaluru - Senior Frontend Engineer

APR 2018 - PRESENT

- Working on the new Design of our Content Management System
- Along with the new design building Design System.

#### Quintype Technologies, Bengaluru - Frontend Engineer

JAN 2016 - MAR 2018

- As a sole Frontend developer, I built the frontend for Accesstype An API driven subscription platform and seamless integration with recurring payments
- Prior to this, I was part of Client Engineering team. We were responsible for building frontend websites that tightly integrated with Quintype. Our clients were from domains like digital media publishing, niche content, e-commerce etc. and had multilingual content.

#### Couple of websites I worked on -

- https://www.theguint.com/
- https://www.livehistoryindia.com/

• Worked on User interface for a Food delivering app.

# **EDUCATION**

# Ujjain Engineering College, Ujjain - B.E. (Civil)

JUNE 2007 - JUN 2011

## WRITING

- Thinking in CSS Grid (This article got published in Statuscode Publication of medium.com)
- Handling CSS at scale
- CSS Grids All about fr units
- A 7 Nights 8 Days trip to Tawang (Arunachal Pradesh) Northeast India